The prize for winning the title of Princess Lily White is Demon Snuff?
沒想到白百合公主的獎品是魔香
How dare she bully my cute junior.
竟敢欺負 我可愛的學妹
Rachel, can you lend me the dress?
蕾切爾 這套洋裝能借我嗎
Good evening, gentlemen.
各位紳士好
I'M THE VILLAINESS, SO I'M TAMING THE FINAL BOSS!
《因為是反派大小姐》 《所以養了魔王》
THE VILLAINESS' MISDEEDS ARE EXPOSED
(反派大小姐揭露惡事)
Does the school have such a beautiful girl?
學校裡有這麼漂亮的女生嗎
-How pretty. -So beautiful.
-好美喔 -太漂亮了
This might be a prestigious school, but it is still a school game.
雖說是名校 但也不過是校內遊戲一環
It's nothing much for someone like me who is used to social events.
而我經常在社交界裡打滾 完全不是我的對手
Judges, I leave myself in your capable hands this evening.
各位評審 今晚還請多指教
What a graceful form.
真是優雅的禮儀
Thank you, Lady Reuss.
謝謝露易絲夫人的誇獎
I've learned a lot from the book you authored, "The Rules and Radiance of Gentlewomen".
您著作的"淑女的領悟與光輝" 讓我獲益良多
You've read my book? I'm so happy.
妳讀過我寫的書 我好高興
Everyone from the student council. Good evening.
各位學生會成員 你們好
What a lovely night.
真是美好的夜晚
Am I dreaming?
我正在做夢嗎
It hurts.
好痛
What do I do? My heart is racing.
怎麼辦 我的心跳好快
Even me...
連我也…
He's even prettier than I imagined.
比我想像中的還要美
Is there anything you needed from me?
找我有什麼事嗎
Isn't there a dance assessment later?
之後要審查社交舞吧
Would you dance with me?
要不要跟我一起跳舞
How can you get a head start?
你…怎麼可以偷跑
My eyes... Something's wrong with them.
眼睛…我的眼睛好奇怪
Should I get them examined?
是不是該檢查一下…
Lovely lady.
美麗的淑女
Please honour me with a dance.
請與我共舞一曲吧
As expected of the final boss of the sequel.
不愧是2的最後大魔王
That's a pass.
合格
Have you heard?
妳聽說了嗎
Lady Selena was pushed down the stairs.
塞蕾娜小姐被推下樓
It was her, right?
就是她吧
Do you want some juice?
要喝嗎 果汁
Thank you.
謝謝
I didn't get to invite a girl who attended a banquet alone in the past.
以前 我沒能邀請 單獨出現在晚宴中的女性
I wanted to greet her
我很想跟她打聲招呼
but I couldn't move when the time came.
但在關鍵時刻我卻動不了
I'm such a coward.
很遜吧
That's not true.
沒這回事
You did well.
做得很好
You helped me when I needed it most.
你曾在我需要幫助時 拉了我一把
So, please hold your head high.
所以請抬頭挺胸吧
You need to be a different kind of girl
那麼…你要成為跟她不同的…
compared to her.
好女人喔
Thank you. I feel much better.
謝啦 我感覺好多了
What have I done?
我做了什麼啊
Isn't this Rachel?
這不是蕾切爾嗎
Lady Selena.
塞蕾娜小姐
What a pity. You couldn't participate in the Princess Lily White contest.
真可惜 妳沒辦法參加 白百合公主選美比賽
I think you would do well if you had participated in it.
如果是妳的話 應該能得到不錯的成績
She is here to see how frustrated I am
她想看到我不甘心的模樣
because she is basking herself in the feeling that she's won against me.
因為她已沉浸在贏過我的氣氛中
However, she will probably win the contest.
不過 應該是她會贏吧
Although I don't know who she is,
雖然不知道她是誰
I don't think I'm really suitable to be Princess Lily White after thinking about it.
我仔細想過了 我不是白百合公主的料
It's frustrating to lose to other people, right?
輸給別人 很不甘心吧
I would've run away if I were you, Lady Selena.
如果我是塞蕾娜小姐的話 早就逃走了
I'm glad that you understand.
很高興妳理解我的心情
This year's Princess Lily White.
今年的白百合公主
Entry number seven!
是七號小姐
This is the prize for this year's Princess Lily White.
這是送給今年白百合公主的獎品
Finally, Princess Lily White will grace us with her dance...
最後 是白百合公主 獻給大家的舞步
If you'll excuse me...
失禮了
Princess Lily White!
白百合公主
An item from the East.
是東方的精品
An incense burner.
香爐
Inside it is...
裡面是…
It's empty.
空的
Seems like the anonymous letter sent to the capital was just a prank.
看樣子 寄到皇都的匿名信 只是虛驚一場
It feels like we are being toyed with.
似乎被玩弄了
Something terrible is going on in the hall...
不好了 會場裡…
Everyone. Please listen to me.
各位 請聽我說
Ashtart is hiding in this academy.
阿斯塔蒂潛伏在學園裡
Ashtart?
阿斯塔蒂
That's...
那是…
It's a demon that we've been hearing about recently.
是最近很常聽到的魔物
Demon Snuff!
魔香
I will unmask Ashtart
我會揭露阿斯塔蒂的真面目
and pass my judgement on it!
讓牠接受制裁
Demon, show yourself!
魔物啊 現身吧
Run! The smoke is poisonous!
快逃 這陣煙有毒
Don't inhale the smoke! Run!
別吸進毒煙 快逃
President James!
賽姆斯會長
James?
賽姆斯
So it was you, President James.
原來是賽姆斯會長啊
James, you...
賽姆斯 你…
Auguste! Hurry! Defeat him with the holy sword!
奧古斯特 快 用聖劍打倒牠
James.
賽姆斯
Turns out it was you.
沒想到是你
Stop!
住手
We have to kill the demon
我們必須打倒魔物
even if it used to be our friend.
就算牠是我們的朋友
The church did send demon-hunting assassins into the academy.
原來教會真的派了 專門暗殺魔物的殺手進學園
President James, stop!
賽姆斯會長 住手
Come back to your senses, James!
快恢復意識 賽姆斯
Let go!
放開我
Let go. I'm already...
放手 我已經…
I told you I would protect you.
我說過我會保護你
Believe in me!
相信我
I won't allow a demon to be killed in the academy.
我可不允許 有魔物在學園裡被殺死
If you have no place you belong to, just stay by my side.
沒有容身之處的話 就到我身邊吧
Believe in me and accept me!
相信我 接受我吧
James!
賽姆斯
I have a place I belong to as well?
我也有…容身之處了…
The demon is still alive.
魔物還活著
Auguste, kill him with the holy sword!
奧古斯特 快用聖劍給牠致命一擊
Selena, what are you talking about?
塞蕾娜 妳在說什麼
I heard the holy sword...
因為 我聽說聖劍…
Is in your hands...
在你手上…
Answer me. Why do you have the Demon Snuff?
回答我 妳為什麼有魔香
Demon Snuff? What's that?
魔香 那是什麼
He's the one at fault.
有問題的是那傢伙吧
No. You are the one at fault!
才不是 有問題的是妳
James did nothing
賽姆斯什麼都沒做
but you turned him into a demon.
可是卻被妳變成魔物了
All of you won't be a demon's ally, right?
學長們 不會當魔物的夥伴吧
We don't remember becoming your allies.
我們不記得當過妳的夥伴
Besides, James is human now.
而且現在賽姆斯是人類
Our instructions are not to kill humans.
我們收到的命令並非殺死人類
What? That's weird.
怎麼會這樣 太奇怪了
I only followed the letter...
我只是照著信上寫的…
Look...
快看…
It's a horde of demons.
是魔物群
They are attracted by the Demon Snuff.
被魔香引過來的
Run!
你們快逃
I will think of something.
我來想辦法
Aili.
小艾
What are you talking about?
你胡說什麼
Sorry for the late introduction.
我太晚自我介紹了
My name is
我的名字是
Aileen Lauren Dautriche,
愛琳 羅倫 多德勒
the Holy Sword Maiden.
是聖劍少女
Holy Sword, you mustn't kill the demons.
聖劍 不能殺了魔物
Don't kill the demons but save the humans.
不能殺死魔物 但也要救人類
That's right. I'm going to be the Demon King's wife.
沒錯 我是要成為魔王妻子的女人
What are you doing?
妳在做什麼
Master Claude...
庫…庫洛德大人
My dear Aileen.
我親愛的愛琳
You should be in the capital.
妳應該在皇都才對
AUGUSTE ZELM
(奧古斯特 謝姆)
MAIN CHARACTER IN "REGALIA OF SAINTS, DEMONS AND MAIDENS 2"
(聖與魔與少女的雷加利亞2) (主要角色)
VICE PRESIDENT OF MISHA ACADEMY'S STUDENT COUNCIL
(迷夏學園的學生副會長)
IN THE AUGUSTE ROUTE, HE BORROWED THE HOLY SWORD FROM LILIA
(在奧古斯特路線中) (她跟莉莉安借了聖劍)
AND DEFEATED JAMES, THE FINAL BOSS WHO TURNED INTO A DEMON.
(最後打倒變成魔物的) (大魔王賽姆斯)
The Demon Snuff chaos ended thanks to Master Claude.
魔香騷動 因庫洛德大人 最後終於解決了
However, Master Claude saw me, yet he didn't approach me.
可是 庫洛德大人看到了出逃的我 卻不追上來
Seemed like he was really angry.
看樣子 他真的很生氣
The person in the duck costume...
穿著鴨子布偶裝的傢伙
Is actually the Demon King's fiancee...
就是魔王的未婚妻
And also the Holy Sword Maiden...
也是聖劍少女
It's incredible.
太厲害了
I did many rude things...
我做了許多失禮的事…
Whether you are a man or a woman, I don't...
不論愛琳小姐是男是女 我都…
Excuse me. Why are you bringing the duck costume?
請問…為什麼要帶鴨子
I thought the duck might distract Master Claude from his anger.
因為我覺得鴨子 或許能分散庫洛德大人的怒氣
The Demon King closes his heart.
魔王把心封閉起來了
It's over!
完蛋了
Nice timing.
妳來得正好
I've been feeling lonely since it's so empty inside.
裡面空空的 好寂寞喔
Empty... Are you talking about the prison?
空空的… 是指牢裡嗎
Lady Aileen. This is the greatest prison in the world.
愛琳小姐 這是世界上最棒的監獄
Go in. I'm sure it looks good with you inside.
快進去吧 一定很適合妳
Master Claude, I'm not a criminal!
庫洛德大人 我不是罪人
Aileen, you are important to me.
愛琳 我很珍惜妳
I have been spoiling you but this won't do.
所以事事順從妳 但這可不行
I didn't expect you to dress as a boy and sneaked into the academy.
沒想到妳居然女扮男裝 混入學園裡
I finally know why the duck has been concerning me.
我終於知道為什麼這麼在意鴨子了
I'm relieved now.
可以放心了
Finally, I can see your crying face.
終於 能看到妳哭泣的臉龐了
I... only did the right thing
我…身為即將成為妳妻子的女人
as the woman who'll become your wife.
只是做了正確的事
You know about the Demon Snuff, right?
你知道魔香吧
What if it had affected you?
萬一魔香波及到你怎麼辦
Do you want me to suffer what I went through when Master Cedric set you up?
難道你想讓我重新遭遇 塞多利克大人設計你的事嗎
Do you expect me to sit in the capital and wait while doing nothing?
你覺得我能在皇都癡癡的等你嗎
Demon King. Aileen worried about you.
魔王大人 其實 愛琳真的很擔心您
That was why I couldn't tell you.
所以我才不能說
Sorry.
對不起
She isn't someone obedient.
她又不是乖乖聽話的傢伙
You knew that, don't you?
你早就知道了吧
Since you are his fiance, you should just use a rope and tie her by your side.
既然你是他未婚夫 就拿繩子把她綁在身邊
That's true. You are right.
是啊 說得沒錯
I'll have to punish you later.
之後再好好懲罰妳吧
Well,
好了
you seemed to have increased the number of pets.
寵物似乎又增加了
Master Claude.
庫洛德大人
I think James is a talent you need to build this new era.
我認為賽姆斯 是創造新時代的重要人才
Is this what you meant when you said I have a place I belong?
難道 妳說給我的容身之處是…
James. Are you all right?
賽姆斯 你還好嗎
Well, congratulations on finding a new job.
呃…恭喜你找到工作了
Are you kidding me? I haven't agreed to it!
開什麼玩笑 我還沒答應
Auguste, are you willing to become my knight?
奧古斯特 你願不願意當我的騎士
I've been looking for a knight like you.
我一直在尋找像你這樣的騎士
Rachel, are you willing to be my aide?
蕾切爾 妳願不願意當我的侍女
Me?
我嗎
I've been looking for an aide who will fight alongside me.
我一直在尋找 能跟我並肩作戰的侍女
Also...
還有…
We are people from the church.
我們是教會的人…
I'll just make arrangements with the church then.
那我就向教會出手
I have the dirt on the church during the swordsmanship contest.
在劍術大賽時 抓到了教會的弱點
I'm sure the church will sell you to me.
教會一定會把你們賣給我
We...
我們…
Got sold to the Demon King.
被賣給魔王了
What's remaining is Selena who escaped.
最後 就剩下逃走的塞蕾娜
She has already been captured.
她已經被拘禁起來了
What is the reason for that?
原因是什麼
Demon Snuff. She smells of Demon Snuff.
魔香 她身上傳來魔香的味道
So, I've been cautious around her.
所以我對她有所警戒
I just didn't show it to her.
只是表面上不讓她發覺
Selena didn't know what Demon Snuff is yet she had been bringing it with her.
塞蕾娜不知道魔香是什麼 就帶在身上
Demon Snuff? What's that?
魔香 那是什麼
Auguste being the Holy Knight is also a part of the game's plot.
奧古斯特是聖劍士 也是遊戲中的設定
I heard the holy sword...
因為 我聽說聖劍…
Is in your hands...
在你手上…
That means she only followed the instructions of someone who knows about the game.
也就是說她只是聽從 有遊戲知識的人的指示
What? That's weird.
怎麼會這樣 太奇怪了
I only followed the letter...
我只是照著信上寫的…
Letter.
信
The person who would send her a letter...
會寄給她信的人…
That person is...
是誰…
Sorry. She idolises the Holy Sword Maiden.
抱歉 她很崇拜聖劍少女
She even communicates with Miss Lilia through letters.
崇拜到甚至跟莉莉安小姐通信呢
I know.
我知道了
The culprit behind this incident...
這次事件的犯人…
Ashtart's identity is...
阿斯塔蒂的真面目…
Lady Aileen.
愛琳小姐
You've returned from Mirchetta already.
妳從米爾契塔回來啦
Were you testing me?
妳…在測試我
Testing to see if I have knowledge of the game.
測試我有沒有遊戲中的知識
To see if I'm the same as you, having memories from my past life.
是否跟妳一樣 擁有前世的記憶
When did you regain your memory?
妳什麼時候恢復記憶的
Well...
這個嘛…
Since Lady Aileen met Master Cedric.
從愛琳小姐 和塞多利克大人見面開始吧
What if someone died in this incident?
萬一這次 鬧出人命怎麼辦
Died? What are you talking about?
人命 妳在說什麼
They are just characters in a game.
他們是遊戲中的人物
Lady Aileen, were you the type who couldn't tell games from reality in your previous life?
愛琳小姐 在前世就無法區分遊戲與現實嗎
This is the game's world.
這裡是遊戲裡的世界喔
Who would stop playing a game because they cared about the characters' lives?
誰會因為在意角色死亡 而不去玩買來的遊戲呢
This is reality.
這裡是現實
Everyone is the same as you.
大家都跟妳一樣
They are humans who won't come back if they die.
死了就無法復活的人類
I am a player,
我是玩家
so you can enjoy being the protagonist of the story.
所以妳才能享受主角的故事
Everyone else's parts ended after they said the lines in their script.
大家都照著劇本說完自己的台詞就結束
That is why I chose you as my opponent.
所以只好找妳當對手囉
Let's have some more fun.
我們再玩得開心點嘛
Lady Aileen.
愛琳小姐
Sorry. I'm not going to play with you.
抱歉 我不想陪妳玩
Are you going to turn yourself in this time?
這次 妳願意去自首嗎
Did I do anything?
我做了什麼嗎
If you have evidence, show me.
有證據的話 就拿出來給我看吧
Do you think you've won?
妳以為這樣就算妳贏了嗎
You are the one who can't separate reality from the game.
妳才是無法區分現實和遊戲的人
If you want to play with me, go back and try again.
想跟我玩的話 就重新再來吧
Lady Lilia. Good day to you.
莉莉安小姐 告辭
Ashtart announced the end of the rebellion.
阿斯塔蒂宣告終止叛亂
Peace has also returned to Misha Academy.
迷夏學園也重回安穩的校園生活
The Duchy of Mirchetta expressed its gratitude towards Master Claude
米爾契塔公國 對庫洛德大人表達深刻的謝意
and gave all the students who stopped the demon attack to Master Claude.
毫不吝嗇的將阻止魔物襲擊的學生 讓給了庫洛德大人
Master Claude expressed his desire to create a world that protects demons and humans.
庫洛德大人表明 願意創造守護魔物和人類的世界
It's a big step towards improving the relationship between both sides.
這是推進兩方關係的一大步
Master Claude, let's go.
庫洛德大人 快走吧
Speaking of which, Aileen.
對了 愛琳
I've been busy with work and didn't have time to punish you.
最近工作繁忙 我還沒能處罰妳
Well...
這個嘛…
How about a kiss
處罰妳的方法
as your punishment?
妳覺得一個吻如何
Let's talk later regarding this.
關於這件事 之後再說
How could you do that here...
你怎麼在這裡…
You've not been prioritising me.
誰叫妳不以我為優先
You just need to look at me.
妳只要看著我就行了
This person
這個人…
really doesn't fight fair.
果然太奸詐了
Let's go.
我們快走吧
The emperor is waiting for us.
皇帝陛下正在等我們
We will keep moving forward
我們會繼續前往
toward the happy future
屬於我們兩人的…
that belongs to both of us.
幸福未來
Regardless of how tough this journey will be.
不論 這條道路有多困難…